麦克斯 那男的要来了
Max, the guy is coming right now.
这是我人生中第一次
That's the first time anyone's ever
有人礼貌地先通知我要"来"了
been polite enough to announce that to me.
呵呵 好好笑 性爱就是乱糟糟
Yeah, hilarious, sex is messy.
速度快点
Now hurry!
在那男的到之前 把小蛋糕放到窗口吧
Let's get these cupcakes to the window before that guy gets here,
麦克斯 他到了之后
and when he does, Max,
求你别转身
don't turn around.
-为什么 -你心知肚明
- Why? - You know why.
这里就是游客众多的贝德福街
And here we are on the much traveled Bedford Street
位于历史悠久的威廉斯堡中心
right in the very heart of historic Williamsburg.
这男的解说超无聊
This guy is so boring.
就像是拿着旗子的催眠药
He's like a roofy with a little flag.
在1830年间 德国与奥地利资本家
During the 1830s, German and Austrian capitalists
在这历史悠久的
established their businesses
布鲁克林威廉斯堡区做起了生意
here in historic Williamsburg Brooklyn.
为了向这些德国与奥地利的开发元老们致敬
And, in honor of those German and Austrian founding fathers,
我们做了威廉斯堡啤酒奶油小蛋糕
here we have our Williamsburg beer-batter cupcake.
来呀 啤酒奶油 赞赞哒[德国腔]
Oof-yah, beer batter! It's good!
你这用力推销的程度
Wow, you're pushing harder than I was
比我吃多了起司便秘 用力推屎还夸张
after I ate that whole brick of cheese.
很快 码头 船坞 冶炼厂 磨坊
Soon, docks, shipyards, refineries, mills,
与其他蒸蒸日上的生意也都在
and other booming businesses opened
日益蓬勃的滨海区纷纷开业
along the growing waterfront.
就像麦克斯自制小蛋糕店这样的生意
Businesses just like Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
瞧 威廉斯堡制造
See, made in Williamsburg.
只要12块95 百分百纯棉哦
Only 12.95, 100% cotton.
我猜我得说 纯棉赞赞哒[德国腔]
And I'm guessing cotton oof-ya, ees good!
我说的是蒸蒸日上的威廉斯堡商号
Actually, I was referencing booming Williamsburg businesses.
而这家是属于威廉斯堡小生意
This is one of those small Williamsburg businesses
很快就会消失不见了
that won't be here much longer.
跟着我
Follow me.
先生 别
Oh, sir, no,
旅行团结束后会有免费小点心
a free dessert comes with your end-of-tour meal
会在古早味威廉斯堡水洞餐厅提供
at the Ye Olde Williamsburg Watering Hole Restaurant.
别浪费你们的欧元了
Don't waste your Euros.
他怎么敢跟别人说我们很快要关门大吉了
How dare he tell those people our business won't be here.
我无语的程度 跟第一次
I haven't been this speechless since the first time
见你脚趾甲时一样
I saw your toe nails.
谁管他怎么想啊
Who cares what he thinks?
我们这个月生意很好 我有足够的钱
We had such a good month, I had enough cash
给自己买一盒夹心饼干吃
to buy my own box of s'mores Pop-Tarts,
这可是我打从11岁起就有的目标
a goal I've had since I was 11.
我当时的另一个目标是能活到12岁
My other goal was making it to 12.
对了 你有听到过我把
By the way, you heard I referenced
夹心饼干称呼为"我的夹心逼干"对吧
the Pop-Tarts as "My own box," right?
麦克斯 我对你的"逼干"没兴趣
Max, I'm not interested in your box.
等十年后我们还是单身猫时 你就有兴趣了
Well, not for another ten years when we're still single.
我真不敢相信那个导游
I can't believe that tour guide
居然跟别人说我们的小蛋糕生意会倒
is telling people that our cupcake business is gonna fail.
的确 我 你
I mean, it's one thing for you, me,
或纽约本地网说会倒是一回事 但...
and Time Out New York to say it, but...
我恨死那个导游了
I just hate that tour guy.
我也恨死了那个导游
I hate that tour guy too!
阿憨 我的天啊
Han, oh, my God!
花了5年的时间
It took us five years,
我们两个终于有共同之处了
but we finally have something in common.
此言差矣 你们俩不都是A罩杯吗
That's not true. Aren't you both an A-cup?
你敢相信他居然跟他带的团说
Can you believe he's telling his entire tour
我们小蛋糕的生意会倒吗
that our cupcake business is gonna fail?
我忠言逆耳一下
Just to play devil's advocate,
或许他对基本的供需关系有所了解呢
maybe he has the most basic understanding of supply and demand.
阿憨 别搞砸
Han, don't blow this,
我们这辈子唯一有可能有的共同点了
it might be our only connection ever.
这狗逼崽子觉得自己是哪根葱啊
Who the hell does that dickweed think he is?
就是说嘛
Exactly.
我恨他是因为他从不带团来这吃饭
And I hate him because that tour never eats in here.
他只会整天推销那间
He just keeps pushing his stupid
傻逼兮兮的古早味威廉斯堡水洞餐厅
Ye Olde Williamsburg Watering Hole.
我一点都不想再听到那家伙的"洞"
I don't want to hear anymore about that guy's hole!
等十年后你还是单身狗 你就有兴趣了
Until ten years from now when you're still single.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
这天真的来了
Well, it happened.
《美国偶像》主持人终于出柜了吗
Ryan Seacrest came out?
麦克斯 别说傻话了
Oh, Max, don't be silly.
他应该好几年前就出柜了吧[并没有]
No, I'm pretty sure that happened a couple of years ago.
我最大的梦想终于成真了
My biggest dream has come true.
肯德基现在买餐
Kentucky Fried Chicken now comes
就送免费接发吗
with free hair extensions?
好吧 是我第二大的梦想成真了
Okay, my second biggest dream.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
不是的 所有在我们店里
Oh, no, everyone just thinks that
吃过意大利奶酪鸡的人都觉得自己孕吐了
after they'd had the chicken parmesan here.
还没正式确定 我还没用验孕棒验尿呢
It's not official. I haven't peed on a stick yet,
但我的胸部好涨好酸啊
but my boobs are really, really sore.
宝贝 那也有可能是我玩伤的
That could be my handy-work, baby.
答案一分钟后就能见分晓啦
Well, we're about to find out in a minute
我要快婊加鞭去尿一泡了
'cause I'm about to go pee like a race whore.
苏菲 是快"马"加鞭
Sophie, the phrase is "race horse."
在波兰不是
Uh, not in Poland.
我买了一堆这验孕的玩意
See, I got a whole bunch of these things
因为我瞄得不太准
'cause, uh, my aim isn't very good.
我小便就是被医生称为
Yeah, I have what the doctors call
"分叉瀑布"的那种
"a forked stream."
你用不到的 统统都给我
Well, whichever of those you don't use, I'll take.
不然每次我心中有怀疑 就得自行滚楼梯
It'll be nice not to throw myself down a flight of stairs
有这个就能少受罪了
every time I have a hunch.
好啦
Oh, all right, well.
祝我好运吧 姑娘们
Wish me luck, girls.
苏菲 稍等一下
Oh, wait up, Sophie!
我帮你拿着验孕棒 你往上尿就行
I'll hold the stick under you while you urinate.
奥列格 你一定能当一个好爸爸
Oleg, you're gonna make a great father.
苏菲还有可能有小孩吗
Is it even possible for Sophie to have a baby?
她在前几年连锁影带出租店倒光时
I mean, didn't that window close around the same time
就到绝经期了吧
Blockbuster Video did?
我们又不知道她几岁
Well, we don't know how old she is.
她是无龄生物 就像独角兽一样
Sophie's ageless, like a unicorn
或像帅哥主播安德森·库伯
or...Anderson Cooper.
卡洛琳 我找到一个城市的网站
Caroline, I found a city website
可以在上面投诉那个导游
where we can complain about that tour guide.
为什么要投诉 他对你做了什么
Why, what'd he do to you?
把你误以为是路边的小消防栓吗
Confuse you with a historic Williamsburg fire hydrant?
击个掌
Up top!
人事已非
Um, things have changed.
我现在跟阿憨一国了
I'm kind of all about the Han and me connection right now.
抱歉麦克斯 你出局了
Sorry, Max, you're out.
阿憨 网上投诉是没用的
Han, complaining online doesn't work.
的确 如果网上投诉有用
True, if it did, they would have replaced
那乐高公司早给我替换次品了
my faulty Legos by now.
要我说得找到他 给他一点颜色瞧瞧
I say we gotta find him and knock some sense into him.
我"硬"[加入]
I'm in.
这是阿憨第一次对女人说出这话
That's the first time Han has ever said that to a woman.
好啦 我能跟你们一起去吗
All right, can I just come?
那个导游不停地用麦克风
That tour guide keeps going on and on
跟那帮欧洲垃圾说这说那的
into his mic in front of that bunch of Euro trash.
就像麦当娜的巡回演唱一样
It's like Madonna on tour.
别管这家古早味威廉斯堡餐厅了
Forget this Ye Olde Williamsburg place.
里面的客人应该来我们餐厅里吃甜点
Those people should be having desserts at my diner!
是啊 如果他们想吃古早味甜点
Yeah, if they wanted Ye Olde Desserts,
那的确应该来找我们
they should have come to us.
我们店里的手指饼干 老到都有关节炎了
We've got lady fingers so old, they have arthritis.
他来了 准备好了吗
Ooh, okay, here he comes. Get ready!
我骗谁啊 我做不来这事
Oh, who am I kidding? I can't do this!
我不是个暴力的人 而且我先说好
I'm not a violent person, and full disclosure,
这是根玩具球棒
this is a Nerf bat.
对不住了 卡洛琳
Sorry, Caroline, I hope this doesn't affect
我希望这不会影响我们刚萌芽的
our budding friendship/ you never know,
友谊/或许还有爱情
possible romance.
下辈子都不可能
Never gonna happen.
我跟阿憨老死不相往来了 现在又是姐俩好
Okay, Han's dead to me. It's back to me and you.
太好了 刚才那几个小时真是恶梦
Thank God. Those couple of hours were hell.
对我来说也是啊
For me too.
我们有话想跟你说说
Hi, we need to talk to you.
我是麦克斯自制小蛋糕的卡洛琳
I'm Caroline from Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
对 我想起来了
Oh, yeah, right.
我刚才没认出你是因为你没用
I didn't recognize you without...
我这辈子听过最烂的德国腔说话
the worst German accent I ever heard.
你怎么称呼
And you are?
达能
Dannon.
达能牌酸奶的那个达能吗
Like the yogurt?
我们家族姓氏就这样
It's a family name.
听好了 优诺牌酸奶
Listen, Yoplait.
我个人是根本懒得鸟你怎么想
I personally don't give a crap what you think,
但你在外面抹黑我们的生意
but you bad-mouthing our business
让我的妞儿不高兴了
is upsetting my girl here.
你听到了没 碧悠酸奶
You got that, Activia?
姑娘们 我说的不只是你们俩的店
Look, girls, I'm not just talking about your business.
是你们那一街区的所有店统统都得关
All the businesses on that block are gonna close.
那块地要开垦来盖巨幕电影院
It's getting plowed for an IMAX theatre.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
对啊
I know.
那街区居然有别的麦克斯[巨幕]要被人"开垦"
Another Max is getting plowed on our block?
早安
Morning.
我真不敢相信我们要被巨幕电影院取代
I can't believe they're replacing us with an IMAX.
地铁站的灵媒还说
That subway psychic told me
我的生意会一飞冲天呢
my business would skyrocket.
不过如果真冲天了
I guess this also means
我大概也就没空参加《美国之声》了
I won't be a contestant on "The Voice."
那个灵媒衣服上沾了一堆食物
That psychic had food all down her blouse.
她连自己何时张嘴都预测不到
She couldn't predict her mouth opening,
更别说你的人生了
let alone your life.
我在给附近街区所有店主发电邮
I'm e-mailing all the neighborhood business owners
让他们到餐厅去参加紧急店主大会
to attend an emergency meeting tonight at the diner.
我联系了几乎所有人
I've contacted pretty much everyone
除了药用大麻店的店主
except that medical marijuana store.
就是"大麻[共同]监护权"
You know, Joint Custody.
我来联系吧 那店在我的快速拨号上
I'll call them. They're on my speed dial.
♪ 夹心饼干 我的夹心小饼干 ♪
♪ Pop my tarts pop my tarts ♪
♪ 夹心饼干 夹心饼干 夹心小饼干 ♪
♪ Pop-Tarts, Pop-Tarts, Pop-Tarts ♪
♪ 夹夹夹心小饼干干干 ♪
♪ A boppa-boppa boppa-tarts- ♪
是 是我吃的 我压力大就吃掉了
Yes, it was me. I stress ate them.
你吃了我的PPT吗
You ate my PPTs?
个人夹心饼干
Personal Pop-Tarts.
你还给它们取昵称啦
You gave them a cute name?
废话 我想吃它们想了一辈子
Of course, I've been dreaming about them my whole life.
我真不敢相信你把我的夹心饼干吃完了
I can't believe you ate the last of my s'mores Pop-Tarts.
好啦 我再出去给你买盒新的
Fine, I'll go out and buy you another box
就用我存下来要买唇线笔的钱好啦
with the money I was saving for a Wet n Wild lip liner.
我们可以确定不是机会来敲门
Well, we know that's not opportunity knocking.
因为我搬来这里后 "机会"就弄丢了我的地址
He lost my address when I moved in here.
你们好啊 姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我的糖没了
I'm out of sugar,
还有你们可以帮我看一下验孕棒结果吗
and can one of you read my morning pee stick?
我看不清这个结果小窗口
I can't read this little window thing
我又弄丢了眼镜 奥列格也不在楼上
and I lost my cheaters and Oleg's not upstairs.
所以你两个出轨男[眼镜]都弄丢了
So you lot both your cheaters.
麦克斯 你听好
Yeah, see Max?
这种玩笑不再好笑了
That kind of joke is no longer funny
因为我们现在要为人父母了
now that we're gonna be parents.
所以不许再开那种玩笑
So no more that!
今早真是不顺心
It's just not my morning.
卡洛琳 要不你来读结果吧
Caroline, why don't you read it?
我就当换换口味
Might be nice to hear some good news
从你的衰嘴里听到好消息也不错
come out of your sad mouth for a change.
拿吧 怕什么
Oh, just take it.
最糟糕的部分都甩我脸上了
I'm pretty sure I got the worst of it.
大家现在手牵手 准备好喜极而泣吧
Okay, now everybody hold hands and get ready to cry
因为我真的觉得超级无敌怀孕了
'cause I feel really, really, really pregnant.
阴性
It's negative.
你才负面[阴性]咧
You're negative!
苏菲 我理解你很失望
Sophie, I understand you're disappointed,
但或许你应该调整一下你的期望
but maybe you should manage your expectations.
我真的以为我怀孕了呢
Oh, man I really thought I was pregnant.
我的月经迟了好久
I mean, my period's real late.
迟了好久是指多久
How late is late?
话题 #我只是帮朋友问#
Hashtag, just asking for a friend.
我也不确定
Well, I don't know.
半年了吧
Six months?
最多不超过一年
A year, tops.
-我想说 到你这个年纪... -小心说话
- Well, I mean, at your age... -Oh, careful now.
在帮我买夹心饼干前 可别死得太惨
Don't be too dead to get my new Pop-Tarts.
你觉得本小姐是多大了
Exactly how old do you think I am?
这个嘛
Well...
如果你张开嘴 回答了任何岁数
If you open your mouth and say an age,
任何岁数 你再也没后悔药吃了
any age, there's no coming back from that.
多大
How old?
这个嘛...
Well...
最终报价
Final offer.
我不知道她到底是多老了
Well, I don't know how old she is,
但你们拖的时间 我都老了不少
but I've aged since this started.
下一位 凯茜水晶店
Okay, next, Cathy's Crystal Shop.
店主已到 谢天谢地
Present and accounted for, thank the goddess.
加伯尼殡仪馆
Garboni Funeral Home?
感谢出席
Thanks for coming.
不必 谢谢 我打算冷冻遗体
No thanks, I'm having my head frozen.
贝德福美沙酮药物诊所
Bedford Methadone and Drug Clinic?
你有名片吗
Do you have a card?
等最后一家店来了 就可以开始了
We'll just wait for one more business to arrive before we start.
感谢大家出席
Oh, and thank you all for coming.
应该谢谢你们
Oh, and thank you
为了这次会议今晚特意闭餐
for closing the diner tonight for this meeting.
我们没有闭餐
Oh, we're not closed.
真没有 今晚我们店生意算好了
Nope, this is a busy Thursday for us.
你们好 是来参加会议的吗
Oh, hi, are you here for the meeting?
对 我们是微笑托儿所
Yeah, we're Smiley Time Daycare.
如果苏菲真有孩子了
Well, if Sophie has a baby,
那么保姆有着落了
I think we found our nanny.
今晚号召大家前来
Okay, tonight's call to arms
真的是事关我们每一个人
is really about each and every one of us
以及我们的梦想
and our dreams.
小生意一直以来都是
Small businesses are and have always been
威廉斯堡的支柱产业
the backbone of Williamsburg.
但今天这事比生意重要多了
But this is about so much more than business.
让我来吧
Let me help.
我上过励志演讲课
I took a class in motivational speaking.
那先鼓励你的屁股坐下来吧
Well motivate your ass back down.
我能行
I got this.
是咩 听众失去兴趣的速度
Do you? You're losing this crowd
比我失去餐馆的速度还快
faster than I'm going to lose my diner.
他说得对 你让位吧
He's right, move it along.
你的演讲让那个无聊到爆的人
You make that boring crock guy
感觉像大热电视剧一样有趣
look like a sweeps episode of "Empire."
我才刚开场而已
That was just my opening.
可以谢幕了 谢谢 卡洛琳
And your closing. Thanks, Caroline.
是的 的确没错 伙伴们
Yes, I said yes, folks.
是 我们都是小打小闹小生意
Yes, we are all businesses,
但小小的店 有大大的梦想
but we are one hell of a lot more than that!
厉害啊 他就像安东尼·罗宾
Impressive. It's like Tony Robbins
和一颗松子生的孩子
and a pine nut had a baby.
我们是一家人
We are a family,
而且唯一 唯一能走出困境的办法
and the only way-the only way out of this crap
就是相互扶持
is each other.
给我点回应好吗
Can I get a "What-what?"
好
What-what!
跟我举手击掌好吗
Can I get a high-five?
击掌
High-five!
好的 击掌万岁
All right! High-five!
真羡慕他
I'm so jealous.
我好几年前就超想这么做了
I've been dying to do that for years.
明天 我们需要你们
And tomorrow, we need you,
你们在场的每一个人
and I mean every one of you,
加入我的餐馆大家庭 一起出席
to join my diner family at that public hearing
布鲁克林法院的听证会
down at the Brooklyn Courthouse
我们要告诉他们
and we are going to tell them
收购的臭钱他们自己留着吧
they can keep their stinking buyout money.
对
Yeah!
就算用尽全世界的钱
There isn't enough money in the world
-也收购不了我们的店 -对
- to buyout our leases. - Yeah.
-阿憨 -等等 他们要花钱收购我们吗
- Han, I don't- - Wait, they want to buy us out?
2万不行 3万也不行
Not 20,000, not 30,000--
美元吗 那我可以移居印度了
Dollars? I could live in India.
这样再也不用卖这些破水晶了
I wouldn't have to sell these dumb crystals anymore.
但我们是一家人啊
But we are a family!
对 我们是一家人
Yeah, we're a family.
明天可能就咱们出席了
Might just be us tomorrow.
多了巨幕电影院之后
With the addition of the IMAX,
我预计未来净值
I predict that the net worth
将比现在这些破旧小店的多得多
of this now dilapidated group of businesses
至少四倍啊
will at least quadruple.
市政专员 你虽然不认识我
And commissioner, you don't know me,
但只要涉及到金融
but when it comes to finance,
其实涉及到很多方面的事时
when it comes to most things really,
我非常有实操经验
I'm very hands on.
同时也是一个傻逼
And also a douche.
休息片刻 然后请反方提出论据
We'll take a break and then hear arguments from the opposing side.
麦克斯 我要问你一个严肃的问题
Max, I'm gonna ask you a serious question
你要如实回答
and I want the truth.
是不是"你能闻到我嘴里有蒜味吗"
Is it, "Can you smell that onion bagel on my breath,"
因为是的
'cause yes.
你觉得我们的开店梦
Do you think our business dream
是不是跟苏菲的孩子梦一样遥不可及
is as far-fetched as Sophie's baby dream?
你知道苏菲就坐在附近 对吧
You know Sophie's right there, right?
不要惹她生气
Don't get her mad.
我有次看见她用膝盖开油漆罐
I once saw her open up a can of paint with her knees.
不是所有的梦 都疯狂不真实吗
I mean, aren't all dreams kind of crazy?
不然人们怎么会称其为梦呢
Isn't that why they're called dreams,
就因为它们不是真实啊
'cause they're not real?
有时你还得在梦中醒来尿个尿呢
At some point, you have to wake up and pee, right?
有时还一晚起五次呢
Sometimes five times a night.
至少你不必再听那个讨人厌的导游
Well, at least you won't have to listen to that annoying
一天说两遍倒胃口的解说词
tour guide's speech twice a day anymore.
也是 请看您的左边
Right, if you look to your left,
那是一家即将倒闭的蛋糕店
you'll see a failing cupcake shop
有两位自欺欺人的店主
with two completely deluded shop owners.
其实这栋破建筑
In fact, the only redeeming feature
唯一的可取之处就是那两个蛋糕婊
in this waste of architecture are the historic Tiffany windows
旁边的那两扇蒂芙尼玻璃窗
right next to those two bitches.
等等 窗户怎么了
Wait, what about the windows?
他真这么说吗 我完全没听见啊
He says that? I totally missed that?
是啊 因为你都忙于把话引到小蛋糕上
Yeah, because you're too busy sprechen the cupcakes.
天啊 那两扇蒂芙尼玻璃窗
Oh, my God, those Tiffany windows
或许年头老到可以让我们
might be old enough to qualify us
升等成具历史意义的地标性建筑
as a historic landmark building.
天啊 我去去就回
Oh, oh, my God, I'll be right back.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
城市档案馆
Down to the city archives.
我要证明那两扇窗户是真古董
I need proof that those windows are legit.
如果轮到我们发言 而我还没回来
If I'm not back when it's our turn to speak,
你就拖进度 消磨时间
stall them. Fill time.
就说个不停 说些没用的话
Just go on an on talking about nothing.
懂了 假装是你就行了
Got it. Pretend I'm you.
但你不可能及时找到证据 除非奇迹出现
But you would need a miracle to find that proof in time.
麦克斯 你有卫生棉条吗
Psst, Max, you got a tampon?
我来月经了
I just got my period.
不是月经 那就是被枪打中流血了
Either that, or I've been shot.
苏菲还有希望生孩子呢
Sophie can still have a baby!
瞧 奇迹会发生的
See, miracles can happen!
那疯婆子就在旁边好吗
The woman is right there.
我已经说了两遍了 法官大人
And like I've already said twice, Your Honor,
我从1989年开始就在那家餐馆工作了
I've worked at that diner since 1989,
好了 说完了
so, peace out.
她还没回来呢 继续说
She's still not back. Keep going.
法官大人 我打从1989年开始
Your Honor, I've been working at that diner
就在那家餐馆工作
since 1989.
我想我们已经听够这位先生
I think we've heard everything this gentlemen
关于这栋建筑的发言了
has to say about the building in question,
不知出于何种目的
including, for some reason,
他还讲了自己和喜剧演员老婆的短暂偷情史
of his brief affair with comedian Nipsy Russell's wife.
她是布鲁克林人啊
She was from Brooklyn!
我认为这跟主题相关 法官大人
I thought it was pertinent, Your Honor.
如果没有其他证人要发言
If there are no other witnesses--
阿憨 快上快上
Han, go, go, go, go.
不要 我已经搞砸了一次了
No, I already blew this once.
终于 你在我不能高兴的事情上
Finally, you admit you blew something
承认你搞砸事情了
when I can't enjoy it.
奥列格 你上
Oleg, you go.
不行 那法官认识我
I can't. The judge knows me
我们在某个杂交派对上碰过面
from a sort of "Eyes Wide Shut" situation.
你上
You go.
不行 在法庭上我从未有过好事发生
No, nothing good ever happened to me in a courtroom.
每一次我都被判回给我妈
Every single time, they just gave me back to my mother.
我上吧
I'll go.
我有话要说
Yeah, I've got something to say.
你是一位女法官
You're a lady judge.
你有经痛药吗
You got any Midol?
如果没有其他证人的话
Well, if there are no further witnesses...
靠 嘿
Damn it, yo!
我有话要说
I guess I have something to say.
太棒了
Wonderful.
卡米拉 我们中午甭想吃饭了
Carmella, we just lost our lunch table.
这模型不错
Nice model you got there,
不过巨幕电影院不是应该很大吗
except IMAXs are supposed to be big.
所以才叫巨幕啊
That's kind of the point.
女士 如果你没有相关的意见要发表
Miss, if you don't have anything pertinent--
停 你们不能拆了我们的店
Stop, you can't tear our building down!
太激动了 感觉就像《律政俏佳人》来救场
So excited, I feel like I'm in "Legally Blonde."
那两扇蒂芙尼玻璃窗已经超过百年了
Those Tiffany windows are over 100 years old,
所以这是具有历史意义的地标性建筑
making it a historic, landmark building.
你有相关文件能证明吗
Do you have documented proof of this?
是的 我有 法官大人
Yes, I do, your honor.
太戏剧性了 我好喜欢
So dramatic. I'm loving it.
活生生 会呼吸超无聊的证据
Living, breathing, boring proof.
法官大人 这位男士是专家
Your Honor, this gentlemen is an expert
最懂威廉斯堡的历史建筑
on historic Williamsburg.
达能 告诉他们窗户的事
Dannon, tell them about the windows.
你先说
First say it.
当着法庭上所有人的面说 否则没门
Say it in the eyes of the court, or no deal.
我再也不会模仿德国口音
I will never do a German accent again.
那栋建筑的窗户是由蒂芙尼工作室创造
The building's windows were created by Tiffany Studios
上面的鱼图案源自最早的威廉斯堡鱼市
in a playful fish motif for the original Williamsburg fish market,
于1901年在该地点开张
opened at that location in June, 1901.
那的确符合地标性建筑
Well, that qualifies as a landmark.
太棒了
Yes!
这真是太棒了[德国腔]
Yah, dis is vuunderbar!
我可没答应过你不学德国腔
Well, I never promised you anything.
你觉得怎么样 麦克斯
How do you like that, Max?
这些来自鱼市的可爱小鱼
These cute little fishies from the fish market
拯救了我们的小店和餐馆
saved our business and the diner.
感觉在鱼市场的旧地点干活好奇怪啊
It's weird I'd wind up working in a former fish market.
达能告诉我 鱼市只是给一家妓院打掩护的
Dannon told me the market was also a front for a whore house.
那才像话嘛
Yeah, that's more like it.
现在我有一个严肃的问题要问你
Now I have a serious question for you
我希望你能如实回答
and I want you to tell me the truth.
如果我们拿着
Would it have been smarter for us
逼阿憨交出来的收购钱一走了之
to take whatever of that buyout money
这样做会不会更明智一点呢
we would have forced Han to give us and quit?
大概吧
Probably.
但麦克斯 我打小就想有自己的生意
but Max, I've wanted my own business since I was little.
这纯粹出于个人情感
It's purely emotional.
不知道该怎么解释
I can't really explain it.
我可以 那是你的PPT
I can. It's your PPT.
你的个人夹心饼干
Your personal Pop-Tart.
没错 是我的PPT
It is. It's my PPT.
那我就完全懂了
Then I totally get it.
是的 你懂的 麦克斯 你最懂我了
Yeah, you do, Max. You always do.
姑娘们 正式宣布了
Well, girls, it's official.
你还是个矮子吗
You're still short?
我们赢了
We won!
整个街区接到通知
The entire neighborhood has just been notified
不会被巨幕影院收购
there is no IMAX buyout.
是啊 然而他们看起来并不高兴
Yep, and they do not look happy.
他们来了
Here they come.
-你个小混蛋 -死矮子
- Hey, you! - Yeah, you!
快开窗 他们拿着棍子呢
Open up! They have sticks!
不能把他扔外面 是吧
Can't leave him out there, can we?
天啊
Aah! Oh, God!